# **EDUARDO MONDACA**

#### **PORTFOLIO**

https://eduardomondacareyes.github.io/Eduar do-Mondaca-UxUi-Portfolio/

# **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Bilingual UxUi Designer with proficient knowledge in design thinking processes for development, deployment and testing of high fidelity functional user-centered interfaces, and HTML and CSS mockups. Experience with Agile methodologies (Design Sprint, Scrum, Kanban) on marketing strategies teams environments focused on user research, creation, design and management of Adwords and Social Ads campaigns.

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

# **Prototyping**

Figma	••••
Balsamiq	••••
Sketch	••••
Adobe XD	••••
Front End	

Front End	
HTML5	
CSS	
Javascript	• • • • •
UX Research	

OX Research	
Google Analytics	
User Persona	••••
Navigation Maps	• • • • •
User Interviews	• • • • •
Languages	

English	C

# CONTACT



eduardomondacareyes@gmail.com



+56 9 75871125



https://www.linkedin.com/in/eduardomondaca-6264721b7/



Lord Cochrane 181 / Depto. 2307 Santiago

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Copywriter / Digital Marketing Strategist

Prohabit Real States S.A 2018- 2020

- Developed digital voice and presence for the company
- Administered every stage of digital marketing campaigns of the company, from content creation, design, deployment, data analysis and optimization
- Increased sales by 70% developing digital conversion funnel for sales department
- In charge of copywriting slogans, webpage and corporative documents for the company rebranding
- Community Manager

# **Startup Project Cofounder**

Satta Project 2014 - 2017

- Creation of brand design and executive development for the project under StartUp Chile sponsorship
- produced by Satta Project
- Design and deployment of digital marketing strategies

# **English Language Teacher**

Tronwell Institute 2007 - 2013

- English language teaching, covering students groups of all different levels, from elemental to professional and conversational skills
- CORFO / TOEIC scholarship instructor

# **EDUCATION**

# COMUNICACIÓN AUDIOVISUAL

DUOC UC

- Professional skill on video edition software (Final Cut X, Premiere, Avid Media Composer) and LDSR cameras and lens kits
- Proficient experience on full audiovisual content production

# TRADUCCIÓN INGLÉS - ESPAÑOL

# Universidad de La Serena

- Written and oral English professional skills
- Knowledge and experience on different translations techniques for
- various targets (Marketing, Technical, Literature, Web)
  Simultaneous interpretation experience on business and scholar
- Creation, execution and redaction of live interviews

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

- UxUi Design Certification Sence Talento Digital (2021)
- Wordpress Certification Adity Academy (2019)
- Google Adwords Certification (2018)
- TOEIC / Score: 890 (2014)